嘿
Hey.
总共六块钱
Six dollars, please.
六块  我只租了一晚  应该是三块
Six? I just had it for one night. It's 3.
是到八点  现在已经八点零二分了
Eight o'clock is the cutoff. And, oh, it's 8:02.
我觉得你有太多权力了
You know, in a weird way, you have too much power.
你得帮帮我  因为我只有三块
Look, you're gonna have to help me out here because I only have 3.
我可以帮你
I can help with that.
天啊  理查
Oh, my God. Richard?
你好  你好
Hi.  Hi.
你的胡须剃掉了
Wow. Your lip went bald.
谢了
Thanks.
你看起来很棒
So you look great.
是啊
Yeah, right. Ha, ha.
是真的…
No, you do. You...
你… 怎样
You just... You... What?
你有条内裤粘在腿上
You got panties stuck to your leg.
因为我刚刚从干衣机收衣服
Ahem, that's because I was just grabbing some things out of the dryer...
静电的关系
...and static cling. Ha, ha.
不然就是上帝知道  我会撞见你
Or maybe it's just because God knew I'd be running into you...
看到这个大好机会
...and saw an opportunity.
很高兴看到你
It's good to see you.
我也很高兴看到你
It's good to see you too.
《老友记》 第三季  第13集  摩妮卡和理查只是朋友
Friends S03E13  The One Where Monica and Richard are Just Friends
（主演：詹妮弗·安妮斯顿）
（主演：柯特妮·考克斯）
（主演：丽莎·库卓）
（主演：马特·勒布朗）
（主演：马修·派瑞）
（主演：大卫·修蒙）
（成人）
有看到那个家伙吗  他在经典区… 谁
See that guy? He's in "Classics" now... Who?
但我们一离开  他就会去A片区
...but you know as soon as we leave, he's going straight to the porn.
他会租《大国民》…
He's gonna go up to the counter with Citizen Kane...
《迷魂记》和《发条橘子》
...Vertigo and Clockwork Orgy. Ha, ha.
太棒了
This is nice.
对   我怀念这个
Ha, ha. Yeah. I miss this.
我也是
Me too.
你想去吃点汉堡吗
So you wanna get a hamburger or something?
我不知道这样好不好
Aw, um, I don't know if that's a good idea.
只是朋友   我保证不会偷摸你
No. Just friends. I won't grope you. I promise.
我觉得太快了
Yeah, I think it's too soon.
不会太快  我十一点吃的午餐
No, it's not too soon. I had lunch at 11.
好啊   宝贝
Yeah, baby.
你在干嘛  做巧克力牛奶  要来一点吗
What are you doing? Making chocolate milk. You want some?
不用  我已经二十九岁了
No, thanks. I'm 29.
天啊  我得去上班了
Oh, my God. I gotta go to work.
你今天会几点下班
What time do you think you're gonna get off tonight?
我不知道  可能会很晚
I don't know, honey. It could be really late.
不会吧  又来了
Oh, come on. Not again.
我知道  对不起  我跟你打个商量  好吗
Oh, I know. I'm sorry. Listen, I'll make a deal with you, okay?
只要我下班回家…
Mm. Every night that you're asleep...
而你已经睡了… 嗯
...before I get home from work... Yeah.
我会用过去很受欢迎的方法  叫你起床
...I will wake you up in a way that has proved very popular in the past.
如果你得晚下班  我一定会支持你
Well, now, if you need to stay late, I want to be supportive of that.
谢谢
Thank you.
嗨   嘿  菲比
Hi. Hey, Pheebs.
嗨   嘿
Hi. Hey.
看看你  你什么时候  开始溜直排轮了
Look at you. Since when do you Rollerblade?
明天开始
Oh. Since tomorrow.
我在公园  遇见一个很可爱的家伙
I met this really cute guy in the park.
他喜欢慢跑  溜直排轮和游泳  所以我们交换条件
And he, like, you know, jogs and blades and swims, and so we made a deal.
他会教我做些运动
He's gonna teach me how to do all sorts ofjock stuff.
那你会替他做什么  我会让他教
And what are you gonna do for him? I'm gonna let him.
好吧 很好
Okay. Cool.
早安  嘿
Morning. Hey.
有人昨晚很晚回来喔
Somebody got in late last night. Ahem.
嗯  我撞见理查
Yeah, well, I ran into Richard.
什么时候的事  大约八点零二分
When did this happen? Oh, um, around 8:02.
我们聊了一会…
And we, uh, talked for a little while...
然后去吃纯友谊汉堡
...and then, um, we went out for an innocent burger.
噢  没有什么  所谓的纯友谊汉堡
Oh, there's no such thing as an innocent burger.
你会再见他吗  明天晚上
Are you gonna see him again? Tomorrow night.
摩妮卡  你在干嘛
Monica, what are you doing?
她花了六个月的时间  忘记他…
Well, she spent the last six months getting over him...
现在用跟他约会  来庆祝
...and now she's celebrating that by going on a date with him.
这不是约会  好吗
It's not a date, okay?
我只是教他做  带到朋友家派对的千层面
I'm just gonna teach him how to make a lasagna for some potluck dinner he has.
你可能会想要多做一点  因为…
Well, you might want to make a little extra because, you know...
做完爱之后  可能会肚子饿
...you'll probably be hungry after the sex. Mm.
我们不会做爱的
We're not gonna have sex.
懂吗  情况没有改变
Okay? Nothing's changed here.
他还是不想要小孩  而我想要
He still doesn't want children, and I still do.
所以我们会当朋友
So that's why we're gonna just be friends.
脱衣服的朋友
Naked friends.
嘿  你有冰块吗  嘿
Hey. Do you have any ice? Hey.
看冷冻库有没有
Check the freezer.
如果里面没有  大概是用完了
If there's none in there, we're probably out.
你才刚下班吗  很晚了
Are you just getting home from work? It's late.
是啊  但我今天过得很棒
Yeah, I know. I had the greatest day, though.
我今天跟卡文克莱的业务代表开会
I got to sit in on a meeting with the reps from Calvin Klein.
我跟我老板说我喜欢睡衣系列  她就订了一堆
I told my boss I liked this line of lingerie, she ordered a ton of it.
你今天过得怎样
How was your day?
我发现我可以只用舌头  数出我有多少牙齿
I discovered I'm able to count all my teeth using just my tongue.
为什么你的冷冻库有《鬼店》
Why do you have a copy of The Shining in your freezer?
我昨天晚上看到很害怕  所以…
Oh. I was reading it last night and I got scared, so...
放在冷冻库  你就很安全吗
But, uh, you're safe from it if it's in the freezer?
至少安全一点
Well, safer.
我会先确定冷冻库有位置
I never start reading The Shining...
才会开始读《鬼店》
...without making sure we got plenty of room in the freezer.
你多久读一次
How often do you read it?
你难道不会重覆读某本书吗
Haven't you ever read the same book over and over again?
嗯   我《小妇人》读过  不只一次
Well, um, I guess I read Little Women more than once.
但那是经典名著   《鬼店》有什么好看的
But that's a classic. What's so great about The Shining?
问题应该是  《鬼店》有什么不好看的
The question should be, Rach, "What is not so great about The Shining?"
懂吗  答案就是 "太好看了"
Okay? And the answer would be, "Nothing." All right?
这可是最恐怖的书
This is, like, the scariest book ever.
我敢说一定比你的经典名著好看
I bet it's way better than that classic of yours.
好
Ha, ha. Okay.
再看看吧
Uh, well, we'll just see about that, okay?
我会读《鬼店》   你来读《小妇人》
I will read The Shining, and you will read Little Women.
好  没问题  好吧
All right, you got it. All right?
好  好
Okay. Okay.
瑞秋  这些小妇人  嗯
Uh, now, Rach, these little women... Yeah.
她们有多小
How little are they?
小得很恐怖吗
I mean, are they, like, scary little?
钱德  罗斯  这位是罗伯  噢  你好
Um, Chandler, Ross? This is Robert. Oh, hey.
嗨  你这里有口红印
Hi. You have lipstick right here.
没关系  是我的  我们刚刚接吻
Oh. Huh. That's okay, it's mine. We just kissed.
穿短裤不会太冷吗
So isn't it a bit cold out for shorts?
嗯   我是加州来的
Well, I'm from California.
对啊  你们有时候  会突然起火
Right, right. Sometimes you guys just burst into flame.
我起来了  我站起来了
I'm up. Ahem. I'm up. I've gotten up now.
有人要点什么吗
Anybody, uh, want anything?
我要咖啡   我也是
I'll have coffee. Yeah, me too.
总共三杯   好  罗斯  你跟我来吧
Yeah, make that three. Okay. Ross, why don't you come with me?
好
Okay. Ha, ha.
你是怎么了  发生什么事
What is the matter with you? What's going on?
罗伯跑出来了
Robert's coming out.
什么意思  他是同志
What do you mean? What, is he gay?
不是  他…
No, he...
他从短裤跑出来了
He's coming out of his shorts.
什么
What?
他的"脑袋"跑出来了
The man is showing brain.
你确定吗   等等
Are you sure? Hold on.
抱歉   刚刚是要咖啡和…
Ahem. I'm sorry, you guys. That was a coffee and a...
咖啡  我们可以写下来  好
Coffee. We could write it down. Okay.
不  不用了  不需要
No, no. That won't be, uh... Won't be necessary.
怎样  没错…
Well? Yeah, yeah, yeah.
该怎么办…
What do we do? What do we do?
嗯  我想就不要直接看着那里
Well, I suppose we just try to not look directly at it.
像日蚀一样
Like an eclipse.
如果今晚有人赞美我的厨艺  我要说什么
When people compliment me on my cooking tonight, what do I say?
你就谢谢他们  然后买礼物送我
Well, you say, "Thank you very much." And then you buy me something pretty.
好了  我们要把手放到碗里…
Come on, we're gonna put our hands in this bowl...
然后压扁蕃茄
...and we're gonna start squishing the tomatoes.
感觉好奇怪
Ooh, this feels very weird.
你每天都在摸眼球  这还会奇怪
Heh. You touch people's eyeballs every day and this feels weird?
我是摸眼球
Yeah, well, sure, I touch them.
但我也花了好几年的时间  不去压扁它们
But I spent years learning not to squish them.
那是我的手
That's my hand.
好   继续压吧
Okay. Gotta keep squishing.
蕃茄被压扁了
The tomatoes are squishing.
噢
Oh, yeah. Oh. Oh.
天啊  你的衣服沾到了
Oh, gosh. You got some on your shirt.
对   等等
Yeah. Hold on a second.
倒点苏打水  马上擦一擦
Okay, just put a little club soda on it. Get to it right away.
应该…
It should, um, do...
有用
...the trick.
怎么了
What?
你的裤子上面也有
Um, you've got some on your pants.
我会把裤子丢了
I'll just throw them out.
这些小妇人真的…
These little women.
你喜欢  对吧
You're liking it, huh?
是啊   艾咪刚刚把乔的手稿烧掉了
Oh, yeah. Amy just burned Jo's manuscript.
这样的男人一定不会原谅她的
I don't see how he could ever forgive her.
乔是女生  是乔瑟芬的简称
Um, Jo's a girl. It's short for Josephine.
但是乔喜欢罗瑞
But Jo's got a crush on Laurie.
所以是女女关系罗
You mean it's like a girl-girl thing?
因为《鬼店》就是没有  这种情节
Because that is the one thing missing from The Shining.
不   罗瑞是男的
No, actually, Laurie's a boy.
难怪瑞秋得读这么多遍才会懂
No wonder Rachel had to read this so many times.
嘿   嘿
Hey. Hey.
篮球好玩吗
Hey, how'd the, uh, basketball go?
噢   我学会带球上篮  罚球和二十三分球
Oh, okay. I learned how to shoot a lay-up, a foul shot, and a 23-pointer.
你是说三分球吗
You mean a 3-pointer?
噢   我得分比较多  因为我很俏丽
Oh, I get more because I'm dainty.
这里有没有电话   我得查看留言
So, um, is there a phone here I can check my messages?
在后面  你要零钱吗  不用了  我袜子里都会放一点
Yeah, in the back. Do you want a quarter? Oh, no. I always carry one in my sock.
你在干嘛  回到你自己那边…
What are you doing? Get back over on your side of the...
哇啊
Hello.
你好  我是乔伊  我们还没见过  嗨
Hi. I'm Joey. We haven't met. Hi.
很高兴认识你   我是罗伯   好
Uh, good to meet you. Robert. Okay.
怎么了
What?
干嘛  怎么了
What? You guys, what is going on?
你们不喜欢罗伯吗
Do you not like Robert?
你们为什么一直在笑
Why are you laughing?
冷静点   没必要一直想鸡蛋
Calm down. No reason to get testy.
别这样  抱歉
You guys. Come on. We're sorry.
只是罗伯好像  在短裤方面…
It just seems that Robert isn't as concealed in the shorts area...
遮得不够好
...as, uh, one may have hoped.
什么意思
How do you mean?
嘿   嘿
Hey. Hey.
罗伯  你可以把那些饼干  传给我吗
Uh, Robert? Could you, uh, pass me those cookies?
当然可以
Sure.
千层面的反应如何
So how'd the lasagna go over?
真的吗  很好  所以你欠我三样礼物
Really? Good. So you owe me three pretty things.
对   我也一直在想你
Yeah. I've been thinking about you too.
不会吧  这种柏拉图恋情很不容易
Well, no. It's hard, this platonomy thing.
什么…  有这个字啊
What...? It's a word.
对   我真的觉得这样比较好  对  这样很聪明
Yeah. I do think it's better this way. Yeah, we're being smart.
我很确定
Yes, I'm sure.
你真的确定
You really sure?
我再打回给你
I'll call you back.
我们可以当一起上床的朋友
So we can be friends who sleep together.
绝对可以  我们就是这样
Absolutely. This'll just be something we do.
像打壁球一样
Like racquetball.
对  听起来聪明又健康
Yeah. Sounds smart and healthy to me.
我只是好奇问问…
So, um, just out of, uh, curiosity...
你目前有其他一起打壁球的伙伴吗
...um, do you currently have any other racquetball buddies?
只有你爸
Just your dad.
不过是打真的壁球
Although that's actually racquetball.
不过我有个相亲…
You know, I do have a blind date...
下星期二   跟我妹的邻居
...with my sister's neighbor next Tuesday.
你要我取消吗
Do you want me to cancel it?
不用
No.
不要  好
No.  Yeah.
因为如果你这么做  就代表是为了我取消
Because if you did, that means you'd be canceling for me.
而我们只是朋友  没错
And we're just friends. Exactly.
嘿
Hey.
嘿   噢   不要坐下
Hey. Oh, don't sit down.
准备去打击练习场了吗  没错
Ready to go to the batting cage? You bet.
首先  有个礼物要送你
And first, here's a gift. Ha, ha.
哇 啊
Oh, wow.
嘿   伸缩内裤
Hey. Stretchy pants?
最棒的发明之一
Well, those are the greatest things in the world.
如果我是你  一定每天都穿
If I were you, I'd wear them every day, every day.
天啊  谢谢  你真的很贴心
Jeez, thank you. Really, that's so nice.
但是老实说  我不认为自己会穿
But, um, to be honest, I don't think I can wear these.
太紧了  让我觉得大家都看得到
They're so tight. I'd feel like I'm on display.
对不起
I'm sorry.
没关系  我可以…
That's all right. I'll figure...
嘿   你好吗
Hey. How you doing?
好吗   好啊
How's it going? Good.
很好  嘿   瑞秋
Good. Hey, Rach?
《鬼店》看得如何了  丹尼刚进去217号房
How you doing with The Shining? Uh, Danny just went into Room 217.
接下来是最棒的部分  浴缸里死去的女人…
Ooh. The next part's the best. When that dead lady in the bathtub...
不要说   别这样  你不要说
No, no, no. Come on. You're gonna ruin it.
好  我用暗号说
All right, I'll talk in code.
记得那个孩子在走廊  看到两个东西的时候吗
Remember when the kid sees those two blanks in the hallway?
记得  很酷  对
Yeah, that's very cool. Yeah.
所有东西和没东西  让东西变东西  对吧
Ooh. All blank and no blank makes blank a blank-blank, right?
噢  不  还有最后
Oh, no, no. No, the end.
杰克差点用那东西  杀掉所有人
When Jack almost kills them all with that blank...
但在最后关头  他们逃掉了
...but then in the last second they get away. Aw.
乔伊  我不敢相信  你竟然这么做
Joey, I can't believe you just did that.
我不敢相信  她解读了你的暗号
I can't believe she cracked your code.
好吧  罗瑞跟乔求婚  但是她拒绝…
All right, okay. Laurie proposes to Jo and she says no...
虽然她还很爱他  最后他娶了艾咪
...even though she's still in love with him. And then he ends up marrying Amy.
嘿
Hey.
我的是个意外
Mine was by accident.
好吧
All right.
锅炉爆炸  毁掉饭店  杀死父亲
The boiler explodes and destroys the hotel and kills the dad.
贝丝会死掉
Beth dies.
贝丝… 贝丝会死掉
Beth...? Beth dies?
是真的吗  如果我读下去  贝丝会死掉
Is that true? If I keep reading, is Beth gonna die?
不  贝丝不会死  她不会死  对吧  瑞秋
No, Beth doesn't die. She doesn't die. Does she, Rachel?
什么  乔伊在问你是不是毁了…
What? Joey's asking if you've just ruined...
不是由杰克尼克逊主演  他喜爱的第一本小说
...the first book he's ever loved that didn't star Jack Nicholson.
不  她不会死
No. She doesn't die.
那你为什么要那么说
Then why would you say that?
因为我想伤害你
Because I wanted to hurt you.
噢  在这里  我的钥匙掉了
Oh, there they are. I dropped my keys.
找到了
Got them.
嗨
Hi.
对不起…
Sorry. I'm sorry.
我今天过得很不好
You would not believe my day.
我值了两班  最糟的是…
I had to work two shifts. And then to top it off...
我在烤东西时  连一边的假胸部都烤掉了
...I lost one of my fake boobs in a grill fire.
你在笑什么
What are you smiling at?
抱歉   我只是在想  你今天还可以更好
Sorry, I was just thinking your day could still pick up.
你好
Hello.
我超爱这种朋友关系的
I love this friend thing.
（中央咖啡厅）
听好  罗伯很快就会到了…
Listen, Robert's gonna be here any second...
你们其中一人  可以跟他说吗
...so could one of you just tell him?
拜托  现在就得说
Oh. Please, right now.
我每次看到他都会担心  "是不是又松了  在盯着我看吗"
No, every time I see him, it's like, "Is it on the loose? Is it watching me?"
我们不能跟他说
We can't tell him.
不可以随便跟不太熟的人  聊他的…
You can't go up to a guy you barely know and talk about his...
宝贝
...stuff.
没错   即使是赞美也一样
He's right. Even if it's to say something complimentary.
嘿   嘿
Hey. Hey.
准备去健身房了吗
So you ready for the gym?
里面有新的攀岩墙  我们可以互相联结
They've got this new rock-climbing wall. We can spot each other.
我在这里就可以联结你了
Yeah, I can spot you from here.
什么
What?
好  听好了  罗伯…
Okay. Listen, ahem, Robert...
嘿  我们不是要…  对  我们得去…
Hey, don't we have to? Yeah, we got... Yeah. Mm-hm.
我觉得你人  真的很好
I think you're really, really great.
天啊  又来了
Oh, God. Here we go again.
为什么这一直发生在我身上   是因为我表现出什么吗
Why does this keep happening to me? Is it something I'm putting out there?
是我的错吗  还是我有病
Is this my fault? Or am I just nuts?
我不知道该说什么
I don't know what to say.
老兄   这里是老少咸宜的咖啡厅  把老鼠关回去
Hey, buddy? This is a family place. Put the mouse back in the house.
真的吗   就像其他人的公寓一样
Really? Well, it's just like everyone else's apartment.
有房间  有墙和天花板
It's got, uh, rooms and walls and ceilings.
我只想看看你住的地方  带我看看吧
I just wanted to see where you live. Now give me the tour.
天啊…
Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
这里是客厅   很棒
Uh, this is the living room. That's nice.
好
All right.
厨房在这里  很漂亮
And this is the kitchen.That's real pretty.
等等  我不能看卧室吗
Wait a minute. Don't I get to see the bedroom?
卧室   喔   就是很普通的…
RICHARD: The bedroom. Well, it's pretty much your typical...
卧室
...bedroom. Oh, ha, ha.
我们还在门的另一边  我没看到
We're still on this side of the door. Ha, ha. Mm-hm. Yeah, but I didn't get to see it.
真该死  或许下次再看吧  今晚很愉快
Oh, shoot. Maybe next time. Thanks for a lovely evening.
她是谁
So, um, who is she?
就是我跟你说的相亲
Oh, ha, ha. That was the blind date I told you about.
她打来  改成今天
She called and switched it from Tuesday. Aw.
你喜欢她吗
Did you like her?
我只是以朋友的身分问  因为我完全不介意
And I'm just asking as a friend because I am totally fine with this.
你似乎是不介意
Well, you seem fine.
好吧   我非常介意
Okay, you know what? I'm not fine. I'm not.
我怎么可能不介意   听到你跟她回来
I mean, how could I be fine? Hearing you come in with her.
她想看你的卧房
She wants to see your bedroom.
你知道吗
You know what?
我们可以当…
What if we're friends...
不跟其他人约会的朋友
...who don't see other people?
你是说专属朋友吗
You mean like exclusive friends?
为什么不行
Why not?
过去这礼拜实在太棒了
I mean, this has been the most amazing week.
有那么糟糕吗
Would it be so terrible?
即使我们是住在一起的朋友
Even if we were friends who lived together?
或是站在其他朋友面前的朋友…
Or maybe someday, friends who stood up in front of their other friends...
发誓一辈子当朋友
...and vowed to be friends forever.
我们又回到原点了
You know, we're back where we were.
亲爱的  那些我都想做  但是一切都没变
Honey, I would love to do all that, but nothing's changed.
不对  你没有胡子了
That's not true. You don't have a mustache.
好吧  一件事情不同了
Okay. Okay, one thing's changed.
但我们想要的东西还是不一样  结果会如何  我们都知道
But we still want different things, and we know how this is gonna end.
你知道吗
You know what?
我现在得离开了
I gotta walk out of here right now.
因为忘记你  是我做过最困难的事
Because getting over you is the hardest thing that I have ever had to do.
我不认为自己还能再来一次
Um, I don't think I could do it again.
我知道我自己做不到
I know I couldn't.
对
Yeah.
那么…
So...
打最后一场壁球如何
How about one last game of racquetball? Hmm?
小心刺
Watch the thorns. Ow.
怎么了
What?
贝丝病得很重
Beth is really, really sick.
乔也在  但我不认为  她会有办法
Jo's there, but I don't think there's anything she can do.
乔伊   怎样
Joey? Yeah?
你想把书放在冷冻库吗
You wanna put the book in the freezer?
好
Okay.